(Sheldon:)Oh, dear Lord.
Oh, dear Lord.
(Amy:)It's okay.
(Amy:)You made it.
We're fine.
(Sheldon:)That was a lot of puppies.
(Amy:)Let's forget about them, and...
(Amy:)pick ourselves out
a nice turtle.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
Oh, how about
this one up on the log?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I don't know.
(Sheldon:)He kind of looks
like a jerk.
(Sheldon:)How about this one?
(Amy:)Well, he's barely moving.
He looks half dead.
(Sheldon:)I know. I like him, too.
(Sheldon:)Hi, little guy.
(Sheldon:)How'd you like
to come home with us?
(Sheldon:)You'll be living with me because
we don't live in the same house.
(Amy:)But that's not your fault.
(Amy:)Like you, we're taking it
ridiculously slow.
(Amy:)You'll stay with me when he's
at Comic-Con or away for work.
(Sheldon:)Or if they accept Daddy's
application to live on Mars.